thinkfree.com 2009-06-10

# Thinkfree Boundless

## Privacy

EFFECTIVE DATE: MAY 1, 2007 

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the ThinkFree.com site and various related services, including ThinkFreeDocs.com (together referred to as the "Sites"). ThinkFree, Inc., the provider of the Sites (referred to as "us" or "we"), is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of the Sites: 

  1. What information do we collect from you?
  2. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?
  3. With whom do we share your information?
  4. How can you update, correct or delete your Personally Identifiable Information?
  5. What are your choices regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?
  6. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?
  7. Do we use "cookies"?
  8. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at any third party sites accessible from our Sites?
  9. What else should you know about your privacy online?

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Sites’ Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our Sites, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use our Sites.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes will be reflected by the Effective Date above. We encourage you to visit and review this Privacy Policy to stay abreast of any changes. We use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we receive your personal information. Your continued use of the Sites after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy. However, if changes to this Privacy Policy will be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you provided us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

Please note that any document or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the ThinkFree Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

### 1\. What information do we collect from you?

In order to better provide you with our numerous services, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our Sites. 

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on our Sites, such as registering for a membership, ordering a product or service, submitting credit card information, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums or other public areas, entering a contest or sweepstakes, filling out a survey, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the Sites, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our Sites in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. An URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet. 

### 2\. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. 

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you upload documents or send messages through the ThinkFree Sites and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Any documents that you submit to the ThinkFree Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

In addition, we may also collect, or our third party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. This information is ultimately stored in the form of store categories, and, in some cases, specific URLs. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our Sites and to gather demographic information. Our third party ad servers will also provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at our Sites. 

We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide our services to you, as required by our agreements with you. We will also use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our Sites, fill orders, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve our product and service offerings, and customize our Sites' content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Sites’ Terms of Use, Sales Terms and Conditions, and this Private Policy. 

### 3\. With whom do we share your information?

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others. We do provide some of our services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners and other third parties. We and our service partners use your Personally Identifiable Information to operate our Sites and to deliver their services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on our Sites; release your address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered; and provide order information to third parties that help us provide customer service. 

We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners, and is not subject to our control. 

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. 

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information. 

We also reserve the right to disclose Personally Identifiable information and/or Non-Personally Identifiable information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use , take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web Sites, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of ThinkFree, our users or others. 

### 4\. How can you update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information?

We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information in your account online at any time by linking to your account in accordance with instructions posted elsewhere on our Sites. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing us at:

ThinkFree, Inc.  
ATTN: USER ACCOUNTS  
3003 North First Street  
San Jose, CA 95134

Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us. 

We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on our Sites. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups. 

### 5\. What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?

We may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our products and services. If you do not wish to receive such emails, please edit your account information to no longer receive such emails. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our Sites may not work properly in your case. 

### 6\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?

The importance of security for all Personally Identifiable Information associated with our user is of utmost concern to us. Your Personally Identifiable Information is protected in several ways. 

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. 

Access by you to your Personally Identifiable Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. 

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk; (b) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through our Sites cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. 

### 7\. Do we use "cookies"?

When you use our Sites we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our Sites. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your first name to welcome you back to our Sites. The cookies make your use of the Sites easier, make the Sites run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our Sites may not work properly in that case. 

We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our Sites. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We will not provide any third-party ad server with any of your Personally Identifiable Information or information about your purchases. We and our third party ad server will collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad. Other advertisers may also place banner ads on our Sites in the same manner as above, but we will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information to them. 

### 8\. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at any third party sites accessible from our Sites?

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our Sites have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our Sites may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. 

### 9\. What else should you know about your privacy online?

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the ThinkFree Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Thinkfree Sites at any time or in any manner. If we learn that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the ThinkFree Sites without verified parental consent, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

The ThinkFree Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are a user accessing the ThinkFree Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the ThinkFree Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use , you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

In the event that ThinkFree is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

You should also be aware that when Personally Identifiable Information is voluntarily disclosed (i.e. your name, e-mail address, etc.) in the discussion forums or other public areas on our Sites, that information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this Policy does not apply to such information. Any submissions to chat rooms or other public areas on our Sites are accepted with the understanding that they are accessible to all third parties. If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practice of the Sites, or your dealings with the Sites, please contact us at [privacy@thinkfree.com](mailto:privacy@thinkfree.com)
